Welcome to his stomping grounds.
Bambi: The Reckoning is a horror, thriller film directed by Dan Allen.
After a mother and son get in a car wreck, they soon become hunted by Bambi, a mutated
grief-stricken deer on a deadly rampage seeking revenge for the death of his mother and wife.
Xana, played by Roxanne McKee.
Benji, played by Tom Mulheron.
Michael, played by Adrian Relph.
Mary, played by Nicola Wright.
Simon, played by Alex Cooke.
Eddie, played by Ewan Borthwick.
Bambi: The Reckoning is a 2025 British independent horror film
directed by Dan Allen, and written by Rhys Warrington.
It is the fourth installment in The Twisted Childhood Universe (TCU) and is a
horror retelling of the 1923 novel Bambi, a Life in the Woods.
The film stars Roxanne McKee, Tom Mulheron, Nicola Wright, Samira Mighty,
Alex Cooke, Russell Geoffrey Banks, and Joseph Greenwood.
It follows a mother and her son who become hunted by
Bambi after his own mother's death.
First announced in November 2022 as a Bambi-based horror film, the film was
subsequently revealed to be set in the TCU shared continuity.
It started production in London on 6 January 2024 and wrapped twenty days later.
Bambi: The Reckoning was theatrically released on 25 July 2025 in the
United States, and received mixed reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of deer, animal horror, bambi,
the twisted childhood universe (tcu).
The tone is intense and dark and mind_bending.